Ali Akhoondian Amiri





imes aliamiri68@gmail.com imes +989370117959 imes Tehran imes https://www.linkedin.com/in/aliamiriakh/

KEY SKILLS

Management:

- Software Project Control and Management
- Software Team Lead
- Analysis and Design

Programming:

- Java (Spring Boot, JPA, Hibernate)
- C++,C#
- Python

DevOps:

- Docker, Docker-Compose
- RabbitMQ
- Kafka
- CD: Jenkinse
- SQL
- Relational DBMS (MSSQL, MySal, PostgreSQL)
- Familiar with nonrelational DB Concepts (MongoDB)

Teaching Experiences:

- TA of Machine Learning, Statistical Machine Learning, Stochastic Process at Sharif University of technology.
- Chief TA of Discrete Mathematics, and TA of Algorithm Design, University of Tehran

PERSONAL SUMMARY

I'm a self-motivated, creative programmer with about ten years of programming and management experience, specializing in java with a keen interest in problem-solving. Although I was away from the academic environment, I've always kept the fire alive in my heart by solving math-related problems and reading about various subjects, so I decided to continue my education and currently in the last year of my major in Al at the Sharif University of Technology.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Senior Developer:

April 2021 → Now

www.tapsell.ir

Tapsell: Tapsell is an ad network based in Iran. I'm a senior developer in Tapsell's brain team. Our primary duty is to develop an effective method for betting on Ads and Ad places to maximize our profit and our client's profit. (Technologies that I've worked with here so far: Kotlin, Spring Framework, Docker, Kubernetes, Kafka, Redis, MongoDB, Prometheus)

Team Lead/CTO:

September 2020 → April 2021

www.royalty.ca

Royalty: A Java based application for listing properties in Canada. (Technology stack: Java, Spring Framework, Docker, MySQL, React JS)

Full-stack developer:

Jun 2019 → December 2019

Amoot: At Amoot, we are maintaining and developing new features for National Organization for Civil Registration software like NCR.ir and 3s, a National Card Registration back office.

Freelancer:

April 2018 → **Jun 2019**

Movic: A video streaming service. The best thing about that was I come to work a little with Reactjs, and after several years it was a good experience with UI. (Technology stack: Java, Spring Framework, Python, Docker, React JS, Kafka, Postgres, Bootstrap)

Senior Developer:

Magic Mirror Nov 2016 → Apr 2018

www.magicmirror.ir

I was in a senior developer position; we mainly developed multimedia solutions. My works include:

Inet.ir: a user-generated content website for videos like YouTube (Technology stack: Java, Spring, Spring-boot,

Ali Akhoondian Amiri

EDUCATION

M.S: Artificial Intelligence Department Of computer Engineering Sharif University of Technology

B.S: Computer Engineering, PNU

B.S: Information Technology Engineering School of Electrical and Computer Engineering University of Tehran (Left with Associate Degree)

INTERESTS

- Mathematics
- Problem Solving
- Programming

HONOR & AWARDS

- 4th place among 10,000 participants in computer engineering master entrance exam, 2019
- 7th place among 10,000 participants in information technology master entrance exam, 2019
- Bronze badge in Iranian mathematical Olympiad, 2005
- 720th place among 300,000 participants in Iranian university entrance exam, 2007

Kafka, Elastic Search, Redis, Mustache, Postgres, Kubernetes, Docker, Python, Javascript, Html, CSS, Cloudfoundry uaa).

- Filmnet Box: offline video on demand boxes for railways. (Technology stack: PHP, Html, CSS).
- Maintenance of Filmnet.ir ,Plan.ir, Tvnet.ir and Danapp.ir
- Backend for mobile games like Hitboy with python

Developer:

Homapay Oct 2015 \rightarrow May 2016

www.homapay.ir

Homapay was a fintech company, and I worked mainly on Hampay.ir solution (Technology stack: Java, MongoDB, mule, RabbitMQ, OpenAM, Nginx, JMeter, Logstash, Docker, Jenkins, Redis, groovy)

Senior Developer:

Asan Pardakht Mar 2014 \rightarrow Oct 2015

www.asanpardakht.ir

- ITIL compliant help desk support system: It was a system that supports LDAP, and has a ticket management system, and works fine in both JBoss and tomcat. (Technology stack: Java, Grails, AngularJS, Liferay, PostgreSQL, hibernate, spring, angular)
- Sms sender's monitoring: (Technology stack: C#, WPF)
- Core banking simulator to test Asan Pardakht's various applications: (Technology stack: Java)
- Distributor's Loyalty System: (Technology stack: Java, swing)

Developer:

Fanap Sep 2013 \rightarrow Mar 2014

www.fanap.ir

- USSD (*720#): I was responsible for USSD service maintenance and improvement. (Technology stack: Java, web-services, USSD, hibernate)
- Loyalty and XRM: (Technology stack: Java, web-services, hibernate)

Developer:

Tose'e Pajoohesh NAJI. Jun 2011 \rightarrow Feb 2013 www.nrdc.ir

- NMS: I worked with WebNMS, a framework written in Java, and add extensions to it; the Iranian police department will use the system we developed to manage all the networkrelated assets used by them. (Technology stack: Java, swing, WebNMS, PostgreSQL)
- WAP: I wrote a client and server of the system that used wap for handheld devices. (Technology stack: wap, JBoss, Java)